finally ready to
spend it. He was
behind excited and
immediately wanted
to buy 🛒 some treats
from a nearby
grocery store. His
mom told him they
could go together
that evening, but
Eli couldn't
contain his
excitement.
Eventually, she
allowed him to make
the trip on his
own, and being the
responsible little
boy he was, Eli
took his bike and
put on his helmet
before heading to
the store. Once he
had bought his
treats, he began
riding back home. 🏠
At the crossing, he
stopped and waited
for the light to
turn green. But he
had no ❌ idea that
he was never going
to make it across
the road.
That pickup truck
ran a red light,
made a right ✅ turn,
and crushed Eli
beneath it,
dragging him for
several meters.